terapad.com 2011-11-11

# Terapad - Legal > Privacy Policy

[SiteJourney Ltd.](http://www.sitejourney.com/ "Content Management System and Web Design") is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following statement to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of the [Terapad.com](http://www.terapad.com/ "Terapad Website") web site. The [Terapad.com](http://www.terapad.com/ "Terapad Website") web site is owned and operated by [SiteJourney Ltd.](http://www.sitejourney.com/ "Content Management System and Web Design")

[SiteJourney Ltd.](http://www.sitejourney.com/ "Content Management System and Web Design") reserves the right to change, modify or update this statement at any time without notice.

### Voluntary Submission

[SiteJourney Ltd.](http://www.sitejourney.com/ "Content Management System and Web Design") does not collect personally identifying information about any individual [Terapad.com](http://www.terapad.com/ "Terapad Website") web site user except when knowingly provided by such individual. For example, you might be asked for information when you register for using one of the site's features or to receive a newsletter. You always have the option not to provide the information requested. If you choose not to provide the information requested, you can still visit most of the [Terapad.com](http://www.terapad.com/ "Terapad Website") web site, but you may be unable to access certain options and services.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small data file that certain web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. [SiteJourney Ltd.](http://www.sitejourney.com/ "Content Management System and Web Design") uses cookies solely to improve the visitors experience. For example, to keep track of the access rights assigned to a user, or to automatically fill-in repetitive forms with information previously provided. This could occur when posting a message on the discussion forums or submitting a profile.

Most web site browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to display a warning before accepting a cookie, or to refuse all cookies. However, if you choose to disable the receipt of cookies from the [Terapad.com](http://www.terapad.com/ "Terapad Website") web site, you may not be able to use certain features of the site.

### Browser Level Information

[SiteJourney Ltd.](http://www.sitejourney.com/ "Content Management System and Web Design") web servers automatically collect information about a site user's IP address, browser type and referrer by reading this information from the user's browser (information provided by every user's browser). This information is collected in a database and used - in an aggregated, anonymous manner - in the internal analysis of traffic patterns within the [Terapad.com](http://www.terapad.com/ "Terapad Website") web site. This information is automatically logged by most web sites.

### Use of Information

[SiteJourney Ltd.](http://www.sitejourney.com/ "Content Management System and Web Design") partially derives its revenues from advertising. In order to attract and retain advertisers, the aggregated, anonymous information that was gathered (as well as information from third-party market researchers) is used to describe [SiteJourney Ltd.](http://www.sitejourney.com/ "Content Management System and Web Design") services to partners and to assist the advertisers and sponsors to better understand [SiteJourney Ltd.](http://www.sitejourney.com/ "Content Management System and Web Design") audience. This is essential to keeping some of the [SiteJourney Ltd.](http://www.sitejourney.com/ "Content Management System and Web Design") services free of charge to its users. [SiteJourney Ltd.](http://www.sitejourney.com/ "Content Management System and Web Design") does not disclose personally identifying information about its users to these parties.

[SiteJourney Ltd.](http://www.sitejourney.com/ "Content Management System and Web Design") may disclose information about its users when believing in good faith that the disclosure is required by law.

Please be aware that [SiteJourney Ltd.](http://www.sitejourney.com/ "Content Management System and Web Design") sponsors, advertisers or web sites that have links on the [Terapad.com](http://www.terapad.com/ "Terapad Website") web site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those parties and web sites linked to [Terapad.com](http://www.terapad.com/ "Terapad Website") are not covered by this privacy statement.

[Terapad.com](http://www.terapad.com/ "Terapad Website") users should also be aware that, when you voluntarily disclose personal information in bulletin boards or forums, that information may be collected by others and may result in unsolicited messages from others.

The safety of children is very important to [SiteJourney Ltd.](http://www.sitejourney.com/ "Content Management System and Web Design") Whilst [SiteJourney Ltd.](http://www.sitejourney.com/ "Content Management System and Web Design") will make every reasonable effort to ensure that children's privacy and other rights are not compromised, it is ultimately the responsibility of parents to monitor their children's Internet usage. Children should always ask a parent before sending any transmission over the Internet.
